

var triviaQuestions = [{
	question: " Martin had a crush on a school teacher when he was younger. What was the name of the teacher?",
	answerList: ["Ms. Jackson", "Ms. Trindad", "Ms. Thomas", "Ms.Tobago"],
	answer: 1
},{
	question: "When Martin got fired, he picked up a plastic garbage can and threw it against the window screaming what?",
	answerList: ["Radio", "Stereo!", "Noooo!", "Damn"],
	answer: 0
},{
	question: "Martin went on a rent strike because his rent was increased and the landlord refused to fix any of the appliances around the apartment. How much was the increase?",
	answerList: ["5.00", "50.00", "500.00", "250.00"],
	answer: 0
},{
	question: "Pam had a boyfriend that had his own skybox in Pistons' stadium. What was his name?",
	answerList: ["Isiah", "Joe", "Simon", "Bill"],
	answer: 2
},{
	question: "Martin received a $4,000 dollar investment and wanted to build a restaurant with the money. What did he call the restaurant?",
	answerList: ["Martin's Place", "Wazzup!", "Rent Em Spoons", "Marty-Mart's Meatloaf and Waffles"],
	answer: 3
},{
	question: " What was Gina's boss name??",
	answerList: ["Mr. Walter", "Mr.Walker", "Mr.Whitaker", "Mr.Williams"],
	answer: 2
},{
	question: "Who was Martin's nemesis in high school?",
	answerList: ["Pretty Larry", "Pretty Rickey", "Pretty Boy", "Mike-Mike"],
	answer: 1
},{
	question: "Who killed Mama Payne's bird?",
	answerList: ["Pam", "Martin", "Gina", "Tommy"],
	answer: 2
},{
	question: "What are the name's of Shanehneh's two best friends?",
	answerList: ["Laquisha & Renee", "Laquita & Keylolo", "Trina & Katina", "Keisha & Lakreshia"],
	answer: 1
},{
	question: "What are the names of Martin and Gina's exes that they invite to dinner?",
	answerList: ["Joyce & Devon", "Helen & William", "Vera & Dexter", "Tonya & Derrick"],
	answer: 3
},
}];

$('#startBtn').on('click', function(){
	$(this).hide();
	newGame();
});

$('#startOverBtn').on('click', function(){
	$(this).hide();
	newGame();
});
















































